KINEMA CITRUS
15TH ANNIVERSARY PRODUCTION
22ND JUNIOR BOXING TOURNAMENT
WOMEN'S MVP AWARD: MARI OTSU
[helicopter whirring]
EPISODE 1 MERMAID PRINCESS LARA
[bell tolling]
[♪ ethereal music]
[LUNA] No way!
I can't believe it!
So this is where
we all come from?
Wow!
I wonder what color
she's going to be.
-Color?
-Wait, I know!
-She's going to be red, right?
-Huh?
She'll be just like me!
She's a blue mermaid!
-She's red!
-She's blue!
[annoyed groaning]
Now then, you two, don't forget
Father is watching.
Whatever color she is, she's
still my beautiful daughter.
[Rowan gasps]
- [SISTERS] Ah! Hmm.
Time has finally come.
[sisters gasp loudly]
Welcome the arrival of
my 6th princess,
henceforth known as Lara.
LARA, 0 YEARS OLD
[baby cooing]
[♪ gentle music playing]
Lara, I'm your big sis, Luna.
[Luna cries]
[♪ melancholic music]
1780 A.D.
[LUNA] Hey, Lara! Stop!
[Lara gnaws]
You can't chew on that!
Ugh!
She's just like you
when you were little, Luna,
don't you think?
What? No way!
[nanny laughs softly]
I've been alive for 1,000 years.
To me, you're all babies.
But at the same time, you're all
noble beings with royal blood.
-Noble? Lara too?
-Lara too.
Let's not forget, Lara is
one of the Princesses of Light.
Uh, Lara, that's from the
statue of our father!
Come on, let go of it right now!
You're bored of this
castle, right?
Then let's go on
an adventure!
What do you say?
Hmm?
[♪ adventurous music]
[giggling]
Lord Rowan, I have
reason to believe
that your daughter Lara
might be very special.
I sense the same thing
in her that I did in her mother,
her Majesty the late Queen.
It's not just with Lara.
Every single one of my
daughters are very special.
Of course, that's just for
show though, isn't it?
Surely you wish for
the princess's
revival above everything
else, right?
I don't have any interest
in such nonsense.
You know full well that
prophecies are forbidden by law!
But then, you are not Nanny.
[Nanny chuckles]
As if I'd even bother trying to
remember every single law.
Hey, Rowan.
-The witch!
-Grace, it's you!
I just came to visit
my adorable nieces.
You're so cruel for not even
telling me about them.
You've already been
banished from this place.
Yet you still enter
my castle illegally?
You know that girl
is special.
It's pointless trying to
bind her
with your
pathetic laws.
After all, her light could
become the very blade
that destroys
your castle.
You broke the law, and that's
punishable by death!
Strike her down, now!
[clanging] [thud]
[evil cackling]
[♪ dramatic music begins]
Are you bored?
I thought you'd be
happy to be out.
[magical twinkling]
Over there!
Wait, did you find something?
[Lara gasps]
Isn't this... This thing
belongs to humans!
You shouldn't
hold it!
Throw it away!
Human?
Yeah, they're hideous,
cursed beings.
Just touching that thing is
against the law.
[bell tolls]
Good night, Lara.
I hope you sleep well.
So strange.
[water bubbling]
[ROWAN] Lara...
1787 A.D.
From this moment on,
you are now an official
member of the royal family.
LARA, 10 YEARS OLD
Therefore, I bestow
this royal ring
upon our new and
beloved princess.
[Lara gasps softly]
By wearing this royal ring,
you now have permission
to swim in seas wider and
farther than ever before.
However, one area is
off-limits.
You must never approach
the human world
that lies above.
Humans?
They are hideous and
cursed beings.
Whereas we mermaids
have always made sure
to live our lives
by the light, we must
protect our light so
it's never defiled
by those hideous humans.
This is our strongest law.
Lara!
So, what was Father
talking to you about?
Stay away from
hideous humans.
There you go, I knew it.
Father sees
right through everything.
But they're so close.
They live right by the sea.
I think...
I'd love to see them
even just once.
I've heard that
100 times, you know.
You're a fool.
I'm a fool?
No doubt about it.
What do you think would
happen to you
if you met a human?
[♪ melancholic music]
Am I really a fool?
[♪ music continues]
1792 A.D.
Is this?
LARA, 15 YEARS OLD
Where is the prince?
We need to find the prince.
Where is he?
[Lara gasps]
What should I do?
Shall I tell someone?
[gasps]
[♪ harp music]
Prince!
My prince!
[♪ music continues]
Lara!
Oh, what's up?
You tell me.
It's no fun around here when
you're feeling down.
But when you're
in a good mood,
you're a real pain.
-Big sis?
-That's me.
Humans are-—
[rumbling] [water bubbling]
Father!
Huh? What?
What's going on?
I know you have been
bringing back
forbidden human relics
from the land.
However, this time
you've done more
than breach a few laws.
I heard there was sand
and dirt
from the land
in your room.
Is this true, Lara?
I have told you time
and time again
that you are not to go
near humans.
Humans are hideous,
despicable creatures.
I don't get it.
What are you saying?
I wonder if-— well, are humans...
really such hideous
creatures after all?
[gasps]
[♪ tense music]
Why did you speak?
Those words are
far more sinful
than any silence.
You are henceforth forbidden to
leave the castle.
Until you have seen
100 sunrises.
[♪ dramatic music swells]
Oh my, why would I say
that to him?
It looks like your big mouth got
you into trouble.
I never thought you'd
have it in you
to talk to Rowan like that.
Who are you?
She is Lady Grace, the witch.
-Lady Witch?
-That's right.
I'm also your very loving aunt.
Huh? But I've never
heard of you before.
[Grace scoffs]
Whatever.
I brought you a little
present today.
I hope you like it.
A present?
Yes, it's a most
wonderful present.
After all, it has the ability of
granting your most desired wish.
It can do that?
Oh yes, this potion
has the ability
to turn mermaids into humans.
You can't say that.
Your father, his laws, it's all
so suffocating.
Don't you want to go back
to the land
and see that person again?
Isn't that your most
desired wish?
What do you...?
You know, I just adore looking
in this mirror.
It's a magic mirror
that shows you
absolutely anything
you want to see.
I enjoyed it.
Your law-breaking conversation
with Rowan...
I also thoroughly enjoyed
the look on your face
when you met that human.
[cackles]
Oh, so you saw something.
This mirror tests the hearts of
those who look into it.
It only shattered
because your heart
was so deeply moved
by what you saw.
What did you see in it?
What do you want to see in it?
Just what is it exactly
that your heart truly desires?
I'm bored.
This potion transcends
the boundary
between human and mermaids,
and is strictly forbidden.
And I have no intention
of wasting any of it
on a coward like you.
Enjoy yourself.
[LARA] Wait...
You're wrong. I'm not a coward.
I'm just... I'm just a fool.
Even though I know
I have to listen to him
and obey his voice...
I'm still a fool.
[GRACE] Do you know
that we are born twice?
The first time is
merely to exist.
The second time is when we live.
Those are the words
of a certain human.
It's not up to Rowan who
decides, nor is it the true law.
The one who decides...
is you.
Many blessings
to the brave princess.
Goodbye, Lara.
[GRACE] If you take this
potion, you can become a human.
But you must understand
it's only temporary.
[unintelligible voices]
You must find true love
before you vanish completely
like a bubble.
[LARA] I must find true love?
[GRACE] True love is different
from standard
romantic feelings.
It is like a radiant light
that can be only be born
from very deep
within the heart.
[LARA] You mean...
[GRACE] I'll make sure
you meet the prince.
After that, it's up to you.
As payment for my kindness...
I shall be taking your voice.
My voice?
The world above is harsh
yet sensitive.
Just like with your father,
a single word
in the wrong place can be
enough to get you cast out.
But don't worry.
[laughing]
After all, true love is not
a voice, but light itself.
I want to see it for myself,
the ending
of the beautiful story
of the foolish mermaid.
I want to see the true value
of the love that blossoms
between a mermaid
and a human!
I want you to prove it to me!
Prove, Lara,
that this is true love!
[gasps]
Oh dear,
the tragic heroine, huh?
I'm really bored
with this ending.
You were a mermaid all along?
Did you really think
you could seduce me
in that repulsive, hideous form?
My Lara, you must stay away
from humans.
What do you think would happen
to you if you met a human?
[LARA] Maybe everyone was right
about humans after all...
But... I'm in love...
with a human.
I have...
fallen in love with you.
[gasps]
[laughs]
Father...
you said that mermaids
are beautiful...
and that humans are hideous.
But it looks like that
wasn't true.
I guess it's me...
who was hideous.
Oh... What...
What happened?
Wait... Didn't I just die?
What is this place?
Isn't that...?
That's my Father's...
Father!
Big sis!
Where are you?!
[gasps]
This is...
It's a magic mirror
that shows you
absolutely anything
you want to see.
Magic mirror...
tell me...
What happened to everyone?!
What did you do to
my daughter?
I just offered her a potion.
It was your daughter's choice
to take it or not.
[screams]
If she goes
into the human world...
I know that if she does,
disaster will strike us all!
[gasps]
[MAN] Your Highness!
The castle's light!
I've never seen this before!
The law must not be broken,
no matter what.
The royal bloodline
is a cursed bloodline!
The castle is going to fall?
Oh dear.
As you know,
that's none of my business.
You're evil.
I will never forgive you.
However, if things
continue like this...
Well, stop
beating around the bush
and tell me what you want...
Rowan.
It's time to leave
this old castle behind
and find a new home.
And that's why you need my
power, is it not?
My power, the power of a witch!
[cackles maniacally]
You're an evil witch!
When we finally reach
that distant place...
I wonder... just how many years
would've been lost.
Are we all just... destined
to fade away into nothing?
Lara, you will be reborn
one day.
The very last light
that remains within me...
I give to you.
It's you, my little princess...
who must receive it.
No matter how sinful
you may be...
It doesn't matter.
Not one bit.
Because I... I still love you.
[crying]
It's my fault!
All because I made that wish!
Because I want so much
to become... a human.
[sobbing]
I... I'll give up this body.
I'll give up my very life!
Please...
Please, just... give them back!
Please.
[sobbing]
[GRACE] Is it true what
you said?
Lara.
It's you!
This is all your fault!
What's that?
You'll find that it's you
who caused all of this.
I know!
Hmm.
Your father and everyone else
aren't dead.
They just happen to be all
sound asleep.
They gathered the faint light
before they vanished
inside their little seashells.
And...
there's only one being
who can wake them
from their deep slumber.
That being is you, Lara.
I will give you a trial.
It will be
the most terrifying trial
you've ever faced in your life.
But if you're willing
to take it on,
then you must break through
to me with your own hands.
If you want to save everybody,
then prove to me you're ready!
Let me see your story!
Show me your story
one more time!
Lara!
[Lara gasps]
Is that...?
[GRACE] Many blessings
to the brave princess.
[♪ adventurous music]
What is...
...this place?
2026 A.D. OTSU CITY,
SHIGA PREFECTURE
-Hurry up Mari!
-Why?
What's with the sudden rush?
[♪ epic music]
[Lara screams]
This is the first time we met.
TO BE CONTINUED
[♪ closing music begins]
Translation: Sachiko Takahashi
Timing: Andy Ellis Editing and
Typesetting: Ashley Barboza
Quality Control: Riley Dalton
Translation Check:
Sriram Gurunathan
[♪ closing music ends]